{
    "subject": "resource/Joaquin_Phoenix",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthYear",
    "object": "1974",
    "human_readable": "Joaquin Phoenix was born in 1974.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9038535952568054,
            "question": "In what year was Joaquin Phoenix born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7224116325378418,
            "question": "Where did Joaquin Phoenix grow up?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6393156051635742,
            "question": "What is Joaquin Phoenix known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.40522390604019165,
            "question": "Is Joaquin Phoenix related to other actors?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3792143762111664,
            "question": "Has Joaquin Phoenix been involved in any activism?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.30499789118766785,
            "question": "Is Joaquin Phoenix married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3026328682899475,
            "question": "What is the name of Joaquin Phoenix's older brother?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2435578852891922,
            "question": "Has Joaquin Phoenix won any awards for his acting?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.20405450463294983,
            "question": "What kind of music does Joaquin Phoenix enjoy?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1784239560365677,
            "question": "What are some of Joaquin Phoenix's most famous movie roles?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Joaquin Phoenix was born in 1974.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5024_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What kind of music does Joaquin Phoenix enjoy?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5024_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Has Joaquin Phoenix won any awards for his acting?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5024_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of Joaquin Phoenix's older brother?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5024_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5024_104.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5024_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5024_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5024_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5024_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5024_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5024_72.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5024_79.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5024_88.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5024_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "After analyzing the context information, I found that it indeed supports the triple. Here is the structured JSON response:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe reason for this answer is that all four documents mention Joaquin Phoenix's birthdate as October 28, 1974."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents support the statement that Joaquin Phoenix was born in 1974. Multiple entries mention his birth date as October 28, 1974."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}